Guide to the Goodwin J. (Goodwin Jess) Knight Papers, 1896-1988 (inclusive), 1946-1970 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Printed Reference Material
  - Subseries 5. Press Releases
    - 4. Tabulation of the Republican Score, Senator Tenney1951 Nov 12, Accession no. M0245; 8 printed (Box 54)
    - 5. Biennial Message of Carl Warren1945 Jan 8, Accession no. M0245; 15 printed (Box 54)
    - 6. Biography of Knight for Harold P. Levy1957 Nov 22, Accession no. M0245; 2tca (Box 54)
    - 7. Depression Talk and the Promoters of It.1954 Jan 26, Accession no. M0245; 4x (Box 54)
  - Subseries 7. Magazines
    - California Statistics, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Business, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - California History, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Socialism, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Speeches (Misc.), Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Insanity and Criminal Impulses, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Women Criminals, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Party, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Education, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Federal Aid to Education, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Education for the Social Order - Rugg Building America Textbooks, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Student Congress, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Bill of Rights, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Bill of Rights Commemoration Committee, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Economic Conditions Government Finance, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Federal Rent Control, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Hoover Commission, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - The 23rd Amendment to the Constitution of the U.S., Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Income Taxes, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Taxes, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Henry J. Taylor - Your Land & Mine, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Constitutional Revision Comm. - Speeches, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Motor Vehicle Code, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Labor, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Labor Wants Free Enterprise, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 25)
    - National Convention, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 26)
    - Press, the, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - Socialized Medicine, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 28)
    - Public Housing, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 29)
    - Americanism Above Republicanism - Thomas W. Phillips, Jr., Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 30)
    - Through the Politioscope - Murray Chotiner, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 31)
    - Humerous Clippings and Stories, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 32)
    - California History, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 33)
    - California History, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 34)
    - El Monte - Historical, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 35)
    - California State Fair, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 36)
    - Inglewood - Historical, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 37)
    - Long Beach - Historical, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 38)
    - San Bernadino - Historical, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 39)
    - South Gate - Historical, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 40)
    - Electric and Power Information, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 41)
    - General Electric Information, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 42)
    - Mining Law in Recent Years, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 43)
    - Oil and Gas Information, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 44)
    - Pacific Gas and Electric Co. Report, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 45)
    - America's Great Hope Recovery in Europe, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 46)
    - Foreign Exchange controls, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 47)
    - Japan Now, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 48)
    - Palestine, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 49)
    - Poland, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 50)
    - Reasons Why I want to be an American, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 51)
    - United Nations Material, Accession no. M0244 (Box 128, Folder 52)
  - Subseries 8. Pamphlets
    This subseries contains pamphlets from both accessions (M0244 & M0245) of the Goodwin Knight Papers.
    - Weber, Charles M. An Approach to a California Public Works Plan, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      1960
    - Water Utilization and Requirements of California Vols. I & II State Water Resources Board, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      June 1955
    - Preliminary Summary Report - Investigation of Alternate Aqueduct Systems to Serve Southern California Department of Water Resources Bulletin # 78, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 3)
      February 1959.
    - Combined Operations of the Consolidated Domestic Relations and Conciliation Courts for 1959 -Los Angeles Superior Court, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Investigation of Upper Feather River Basin Development State Department of Water Resources Bulletin # 59, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      February 1957
    - The County Jails of California: an Evaluation - State Board of Corrections, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      March 1957.
    - Investigation of Alternate Aqueduct Systems to Serve Southern California, Appendix A, Dept. of Water Resources Bulletin #78, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      Jan. 1959
    - 4th Partial Report, Water Problems of the State of California, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      May 1953
    - 33rd Annual Encampment - Veterans of Foreign Wars of the U.S., Oakland, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 9)
      June 1953
    - Second Partial Report - Governmental Reorganization - State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 10)
      1951
    - The Gavel, Delta Sigma Rho, Vol. 38 #4, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      May 1956
    - Where is American Motors Going? New York, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 12)
      January 1960
    - California Child Care Centers, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - American Motors, Roney & Co., New York Stick Exchange, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 14)
      October 1959
    - California State Scholarship Comm., 2nd Biennial Report, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 15)
      1958-1960
    - Justice Expedited - a ten year Summary, U.C.L.A. Law Review, Vol. 7 No. 1, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 16)
      Jan. 1960
    - State Interim Committee on Fish and Game, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 17)
      1959
    - Medical Quackery State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Report of State Comm. on Collection Agencies, Private Detectives, and Debt Liquidators, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 19)
      1957
    - Report - Comm. on Social Welfare Part 7, Absent Father Problem in the Aid to Needy Children Program, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 20)
      1955
    - 4th Partial Report, Recreation, State Beaches, and Parks, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - California's State Park Program, Senate Committee, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Ohnimus, Arthur A. The Legislature of California, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - State and Local Administration of Housing Regulations, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Administrative Structure of California State Agencies Regulating Business and Commerce, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 25)
    - Proposals for Reorganization of California Water Resource Agencies, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 26)
    - California's Rapidly Changing Mental Health Program, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 27)
      March 1959
    - State Senator Dilsworth, Nelson S. Our Constitution, Have We Outgrown It? State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 28)
    - Report - Senate Interim Committee on Public Utilities, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 29)
    - Preliminary Study - Disaster Protection of Public Records Senate Committee on Governmental Admin., Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 30)
      1953
    - Report - California Comm. on Interstate Co-operation, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 31)
    - First and Second Partial - State School Building Aid and Recomm. on Teacher Retirement Provisions, State Senate 1954, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 32)
    - Report - Collection Agencies, Private Detectives, Debt Liquidators, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 33)
    - Report - Highway Problems, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 34)
    - Report - The Medical Care Program for Public Assistance Recipients, Part 8, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 35)
    - Final Report - State Interim Committee on Riding & Hiking Trails, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 36)
    - Final - State Inter Committee on Regulation of Highway Carriers, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 37)
    - Final - State Inter Committee on Highways, Streets, and Bridges, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 38)
    - Progress - Small Boat Harbors, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 39)
    - Final - Administrative Regulations and Adjudications, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 40)
    - Proposals to Regulate Trading Stamps, Senate, State, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 41)
      1958
    - Workmen's Compensation Benefits, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 42)
    - State School Building Aid and Recommendations on Teacher Retirement ¨Provisions, State Senate 1954, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 43)
    - 2nd Preliminary Report - Joint Interim Committee on Soil Conservation, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 44)
    - Inter Comm. - Licensing Business and Professions, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 45)
    - Horse Racing and Jai Alai, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 46)
    - Report on Judicial Salaries, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 47)
    - Senate Committee on Judiciary, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 48)
    - Joint Inter. Com. - Public Education System, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 49)
      1961
    - Final Report - Senate Interim Committee on Stream and Beach Erosion, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 50)
    - Progress Report - Proposed Water Projects, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 51)
    - Recreation, State Beaches, and Parks, State Senate, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 52)
    - Local-Federal Relations Imperial Valley, Palo Verde Valley Imperial Irrigation District, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 53)
    - Investigation of Alternative Aqueduct Systems to Serve Southern California, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 54)
    - Engineering News-Record, Vol. 152 No. 17 / McGraw-Hill,April 29, 1954, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 55)
    - Water Facts for Californians, State Dept. of Water Resources, Accession no. M0244 (Box 129, Folder 56)
    - Journal of the State Bar of California, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Directory of Adresses, Telephone Numbers of State Depts., Div., Key Personnel and Deputies, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - The Governors of the States, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 4)
      1900-1950
    - Judiciary - Judicial Selection, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - LA Board of Harbor Comm. Annual Report, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Partisan Republicans of California, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Republican Assembly, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Republican Tact Book, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - State Central Committee Members, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - State Organization Charts, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Elections, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 12)
      1946-1950
    - Republican Party - General, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Senate and House Congressional Record, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 14)
      8/20/57
    - Nat'l. Probation Assoc. News, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Political Speeches, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Voter Information, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - American Bar Association Journal, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - The Junior Statesman of American, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Good Business, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Basic Cycles in Business and Investment, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Wings of Healing, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - California Almond Grower's Exchange, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - California State Employees Association, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Elks National Convention, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Alcoholism, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - U.S. Savings and Loan League, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 27)
    - The Miracle of America, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 28)
    - Pacific Coast Outdoor Poster Coverage, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 29)
    - Seventh Day Adventists, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 30)
    - 40 Plus Club, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 31)
    - Boy Scouts, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 32)
    - Hickinbotham Bros., Ltd., Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 33)
    - California Mining Journal, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 34)
    - California Newspaper Directory & Rate Book, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 35)
    - General Motors Annual Report to Employees, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 36)
    - General Foods Annual Report, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 37)
    - Hiller - Model 12C, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 38)
    - LA County Women's Auxiliary Medical Assoc., Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 39)
    - General Electric, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 40)
    - Visual Digest, Accession no. M0244 (Box 130, Folder 41)
    - Pamphlets continue, Accession no. M0244 (Box 131)
    - Pamphlets continue, Accession no. M0244 (Box 132)
    - Senate Daily Journal, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
      1-6-47(4); 1-8-47(1); 1-5-53(1); 3-1-54(1)
    - Senate Bill #522 6-12-57, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Assembly Daily Journal 1-6-53; 3-1-54; 3-5-56; 4-15-58; 4-16-58, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Statement of Vote 6-8-54; 6-5-56; 11-6-56; 6-3-58; 11-4-58, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Information Relating to the State Legislature of California (4), Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Winston W. Crouch: The Calif. Lefislature 1967, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - What You Should Know About the CRA, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Crane, Dr. Philip: The Nixon Administration, The Conservative Mandate. 1968, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Town Meeting Handbook - 1960 White House Conference on Children and Youth, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Sacramento Newsletter 4-23-62, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Public Opinion Surveys of Political Issues and Trends 1945 July, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - California Educational Assistance.. .to Widows of Deceased Vets.l948, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The Payroll System of the State of California 1949, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - A Businessman's Appraisal of the RTW Ptroposal 1960, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Manual for Speakers Knight for Gov. Campaign 1954, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The American Forum 1956 " Will the West Dominate the 1956 Elections?", Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 130th Convention Alpha Delta Phi 1962, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Stanford Club of LA Membership Directory 1964-1965, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Directory of Stanford Lawyers 1949, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Alumni Directory Stanford Law School1967, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Stanford Lawyer's Directory, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Calif. Voters' Handbook 1960, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - California's State Capital, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Dedication of the Memorial Tablet to Frederick Leaser 1928, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - History in Stained Glass. St. John's Church WDC, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Merrill, John Benjamin: Our Presidents and their Hymns. 1933, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Stevenson, Adlai: Red China and the UN, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The Declaration of Independence and the Constitution of the US, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Sacramento Co. I-list. Soc. Golden Notes May 1973 "Families in the Mansion", Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The Book of Presidents, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 1956 Presidential Handbook, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 1964 Presidential Handbook, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 1960 Presidential Handbook, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Disability Insurance Benefits, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Order of Ahepa, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Aqueduct 1973 May, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Dedication of Lake Perris 1973, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Americans for Freedom, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Good Conf. on Children and Youth " The Age of Conflict ", Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 42nd Annual State Convention of the American Legion 1960, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - CHP, 1954 Annual Report, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The Security Home Owner 1953, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Grand National Livestock Exposition 1955, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Calif. Annual Farm Labor Report 1952, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The American Federationist 1955 Nov, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Calif. State Job Listings, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Calif. State Careers for Graduates 1957, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The Ebell of LA 1961, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 10th Annual Western Safety Conference 1963, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - LIVE (survival plans for nuclear attack) 1960, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - CD Shelter Policy 1960, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Brain-washed into Slavery, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - California Centennials 1950, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The Federation 1958, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - LA Examiner's 19th Master Carrier Banquet 1959, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 8th Annual Eagle Scout Recognition Dinner 1960, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Annual Report Lynwood's United Nations 1958, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - Pictorial California 1953, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - The Greek Orthodox Community of Sacramento 1952, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
    - 100th Annual Convention Internation Typographical Union 1958, Accession no. M0245 (Box 54)
  - Subseries 9. Magazine Articles (Box 133)
    - American Bar Assoc. JournalMarch 1957, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
    - ARGONAUT10-29-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.19 Advertisement: Knight is Right
    - ARGONAUT12-9-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.8 Governor Presents Journalism Awards
    - Burroughs Clearing HouseOct. 1966, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.82 Imperial Bank
    - CALIFORNIA DAIRYMAN4-17-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      cover and story p.5 GJK Visits LA Milkshed
    - CALIFORNIA HIGHWAYS AND PUBLIC WORKSJuly-Aug. 1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.43 photo
    - CALIFORNIA HIGHWAYS AND PUBLIC WORKSSept-Oct 1951, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      pp.17/18 + 35/53
    - CALIFORNIA HIGHWAYS AND PUBLIC WORKSJuly-Aug. 1956, Accession no. M0244; (2 copies) (Box 133)
      p.1 + p.52
    - CALIFORNIA MINING JOURNAL 11-'55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.19 Knight-Russell Conference
    - California PanoramaNo date, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.3 Welcome
    - CALIFORNIA PLASTERERMarch '55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      cover, story pp. 14-15 convention
    - CALIFORNIA PUBLISHERMarch '58, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.21 photo Mrs. K.
    - COLLIERS2-3-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.39-47 The Gentlemen From California (+ extra copy)
    - COLLIERS8-17-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.19-21/40-47 The Negro Voter m.GJK p.44 col. 2
    - EAGLEJune 1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.35 Eagle to Watch (1954 White House?)
    - FORTNIGHT1-6-50, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      Cover and story pp. 9-11 re: Warren-Knight breakup
    - FORTNIGHT9-14-53, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.14 re: Gubernatorial candidates...
    - FORTNIGHTDec. '55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      pp.21-22 Four Men on a Dark Horse
    - GAME & GOSSIP v.9 #5, Accession no. M0244; Goodie's background (Box 133)
      pp. 6-7/28
    - IMPROVEMENT ERAApr. '57, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.230-2 Ross Eager Story (iron lung photo)
    - INTERNATIONAL MUSICIANNov. '55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.9 More facts about the 20% tax. photo
    - LIFE9-30-57, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      pp. 22-7 Land of Loony Schemes and Political Extremes
    - LIFE March 29, '54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      pp. 116-127 California's Excellency Excels at Jokes...
    - LIFE 6-8-53, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      pp.30-1 Goodbye Earl, Hello Goody.
    - LIFE 10-13-58, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.43 Phto of 4 Serious Republicans
    - LIFE 10-27-58, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.21-7 Nixon Jolts Campaign
    - LIFE 11-3-58, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.33-5 Parties Fightin' and Feudin
    - LIFE 4-28-58, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.124-136 Calif. Gov. Big League
    - LOOK 10-28-58, Accession no. M0244; (2 copies) (Box 133)
      p.23-7 The Year's Most Important Election
    - NEWSWEEK 12-8-58, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.19 The Periscope: A Job for Knight?
    - NEWSWEEK 8-7-61 p. 19 Will He? Won't He?, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
    - NEWSWEEK 10-2-61, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.30-32 POLITICS: Tossed Salad
    - NEWSWEEK 12-11-61, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.23-4 Goodie's Bad News
    - NEWSWEEK 6-11-62, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.15 The Perisope: Sacto. re: VK and Mrs. Brown
    - Pacific Coast fire JournalSept '54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.3 Fire Prevention Week
    - Photoplay Aug-67, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.47 Barbara League
    - PICTORIAL CALIFORNIAN Holiday No.,1953, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.19 photo GJK
    - PICTORIAL CALIFORNIAN Winter, 1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.26 photo GJK, VK, Prince Axel (Denmark)
    - PONY EXPRESS 2-1949, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.1 Lt. Gov. GJK (mining article)
    - SACRAMENTANJune 1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.7 Governor's Message (box & photo)
    - Report III Feb. 1957, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      Air Pollution
    - SATURDAY EVENING POST 10-29-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.34-5/76-82 How to Run for Office
    - SATURDAY EVENING POST 10-20-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.34-5/120-4 Who Will TAke California?
    - SATURDAY EVENING POST 4-20-57, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)
      p.31 box (GJK on divorce)
    - SATURDAY EVENING POST 10-18-58, Accession no. M0244 (Box 133)